let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which flower is national flower of pakistan?",
    answer: "Jasmine",
    options: [
      "Jasmine",
      "Rose",
      "Sunflower",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many rivers are there in punjab?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "3",
      "7",
      "5",
      "1"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which country and its territory covers the most time zones?",
    answer: "France",
    options: [
      "France",
      "Spain",
      "Germany",
      "Greece"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When was the Famous children's television show \"Ainak Wala Jinn Broadcasted\" by PTV?",
    answer: "1993",
    options: [
      "1990",
      "1991",
      "1992",
      "1993"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "World polio day observed every year on?",
    answer: "Octuber 24",
    options: [
      "Octuber 23",
      "Octuber 24",
      "November 23",
      "November 24"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The Smallest Continent (by Area) in the World is?",
    answer: "Australia",
    options: [
      "South America",
      "Africa",
      "Australia",
      "Antartica"
    ]
  },    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The Second largest city of Pakistan is?",
    answer: "Lahore",
    options: [
      "Faislabad",
      "Lahore",
      "Karachi",
      "Rawalpindi"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which country is called \"Land Of Thousand Islands\"?",
    answer: "Indonesia",
    options: [
      "Maldives",
      "Philippines",
      "Indonesia",
      "Malaysia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "22 April is observed internationally as?",
    answer: "Earth Day",
    options: [
      "Labour Day",
      "Enviroment Day",
      "Health Day",
      "Earth Day"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many districts are in sindh?",
    answer: "30",
    options: [
      "27",
      "28",
      "29",
      "30"
    ]
  },
];